JOINS will make your queries a little bit more complicated.
ستجعل JOINS استعلاماتك أكثر تعقيدًا بعض الشيء.
Let's break down all the parts of a JOIN to
دعونا نفحص جميع أجزاء JOIN
see what they do before you write some of your own.
لنرى ما يفعلوه قبل أن تكتبوا استعلاماتكم.
We'll start by writing what's called an INNER JOIN
سنبدأ بكتابة ما يسمى INNER JOIN
and we'll move on to other types of JOINS shortly.
وسننتقل إلى الأنواع الأخرى من JOINS بعد قليل.
In order to write a JOIN,
ولكتابة JOIN،
the first thing will need are SELECT and FROM clauses just like any other query.
فإن أول شيء سنحتاج إليه هو عبارتي SELECT و FROM تمامًا مثل أي استعلام آخر.
In this case, we're looking to add account names to each order.
في هذه الحالة، نبحث لإضافة أسماء حسابات لكل طلب.
So we'll start with the Orders table.
لذا سنبدأ مع جدول الطلبات.
You'll notice I'm running this query even though it's not yet finished.
ستلاحظون أني أقوم بتشغيل هذا الاستعلام على الرغم من أنه لم ينته بعد.
This is an easy way to make sure I haven't made
هذه طريقة سهلة للتأكد من عدم
any typos or errors in the first part of my query.
وجود أخطاء إملائية أو أخطاء في الجزء الأول من استلامي.
Since it worked, we can move on to write the JOIN.
وبما أنها نجحت، يمكننا الانتقال إلى كتابة JOIN.
The next thing we need is a JOIN clause.
الشيء التالي الذي نحتاجه هو عبارة JOIN.
You can think of this like a second FROM clause.
يمكنكم التفكير في العبارة الثانية FROM.
It identifies the table where the data that we want to join lives.
فهو يحدد الجدول الموجود فيها البيانات التي نريد ضمها.
In this case, account names live in the Accounts table,
في هذه الحالة، توجد أسماء الحسابات في جدول الحسابات،
so that's what we've written.
وهو ما كتبناه.
Finally, we need to specify the relationship between the two tables.
وأخيرًا، نحتاج إلى تحديد العلاقة بين الجدولين.
This happens by writing a logical statement in the ON clause.
يحدث هذا بكتابة عبارة منطقية في عبارة ON.
Now that the join is complete,
الآن بعد اكتمال الربط،
let's add some columns from the Accounts table
دعونا نضيف بعض الأعمدة من جدول الحسابات
into our SELECT statement to complete the query.
إلى عبارة SELECT لإكمال الاستعلام.
You can see that the results now contain information
يمكنكم رؤية أن النتائج تحتوي الآن على معلومات
about the orders and the accounts that placed them.
حول الحسابات والحسابات التي وضعناها.